Guide to the Reginald Sellman negatives, 1911-1935
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- Reginald Sellman negatives, 1911-1935, (3 boxes)
  - Bruce Darden Sellman, H.W. of Md., 1919 June 22 (Box 2, Image 513)
  - Bruce Darden Sellman, H.W. of Md., 1919 June 22 (Box 2, Image 514)
  - Bruce Darden Sellman, home, 1919 July 11 (Box 2, Image 515)
    Next images are badly faded.
  - Bruce Darden Sellman, home, 1919 July 11 (Box 2, Image 516)
  - Bruce Darden Sellman, home, 1919 July 11 (Box 2, Image 517)
  - Bruce Darden Sellman, home, 1919 July 11 (Box 2, Image 518)
  - Bruce Darden Sellman, home, 1919 July 11 (Box 2, Image 519)
  - Bruce Darden Sellman, home, 1919 July 11 (Box 2, Image 520)
  - Bruce Darden Sellman, front porch, 1919 July 27 (Box 2, Image 521)
  - Bruce Darden Sellman, front porch, 1919 July 27 (Box 2, Image 522)
  - Bruce Darden Sellman, front porch, 1919 July 27 (Box 2, Image 523)
  - Bruce Darden Sellman, with mother, front porch, 1919 July 27 (Box 2, Image 524)
  - No negative for 525 (Bruce Darden Sellman, with mother, front porch, 1919 July 27). See card index entry for details. (Box 2)
  - Bruce Darden Sellman, with father, front porch, 1919 July 27 (Box 2, Image 526)
  - Bruce Darden Sellman, with father, front porch, 1919 July 27 (Box 2, Image 527)
  - Bruce Darden Sellman, with father, in bath, 1919 July 29 (Box 2, Image 528)
  - Bruce Darden Sellman, in scales in home, 1919 July 29 (Box 2, Image 529)
  - Bruce Darden Sellman, 1919 July 29 (Box 2, Image 530)
  - Bruce Darden Sellman on back porch, 1919 Nov. 2 (Box 2, Image 531)
  - B.D.S. and R.O.S. on back porch, 1919 Nov. 2 (Box 2, Image 532)
  - B.D.S. and R.O.S. on back porch, 1919 Nov. 2 (Box 2, Image 533)
  - B.D.S. in carriage, 1919 Nov. 2 (Box 2, Image 534)
  - B.D.S. in carriage, 1919 Nov. 2 (Box 2, Image 535)
  - B.D.S. in carriage, 1919 Nov. 2 (Box 2, Image 536)
  - B.D.S. and O.D.S. in bedroom, 1919 Nov. 2 (Box 2, Image 537)
  - B.D.S and R.O.S. in bedroom, 1919 Nov. 2 (Box 2, Image 538)
  - B.D.S and R.O.S. in bedroom, 1919 Nov. 2 (Box 2, Image 539)
  - B.D.S. and O.D.S. in bedroom, 1920 Jan. 24 (Box 2, Image 540)
  - 1919 Christmas garden, 1920 Feb. 9 (Box 2, Image 541)
  - B.D.S., 1920 Feb. 9 (Box 2, Image 542)
  - B.D.S., 1920 Feb. 9 (Box 2, Image 543)
  - B.D.S., 1920 Feb. 9 (Box 2, Image 544)
  - B.D.S., 1920 Feb. 9 (Box 2, Image 545)
  - B.D.S., 1920 Feb. 9 (Box 2, Image 546)
  - B.D.S., 1920 Feb. 9 (Box 2, Image 547)
  - B.D.S., 1920 Feb. 9 (Box 2, Image 548)
  - B.D.S., 1920 Feb. 9 (Box 2, Image 549)
  - B.D.S., 1920 Feb. 9 (Box 2, Image 550)
  - B.D.S. with toys, 1920 Feb. (Box 2, Image 551)
  - B.D.S. with toys, 1920 Feb. (Box 2, Image 552)
  - B.D.S. with toys, 1920 Feb. (Box 2, Image 553)
  - B.D.S. with toys, 1920 Feb. (Box 2, Image 554)
  - B.D.S. before haircut, 1920 Feb. 27 (Box 2, Image 555)
  - B.D.S. before haircut, 1920 Feb. 27 (Box 2, Image 556)
  - B.D.S. before haircut, 1920 Feb. 27 (Box 2, Image 557)
  - B.D.S. before haircut, 1920 Feb. 27 (Box 2, Image 558)
  - Bruce after first haircut, 1920 Mar. 2 (Box 2, Image 559)
  - Bruce after first haircut, 1920 Mar. 2 (Box 2, Image 560)
  - Bruce and Thelma in back yard, 1920 June 1 (Box 2, Image 561)
  - Bruce in back yard, 1920 June 1 (Box 2, Image 562)
  - Bruce in back yard, 1920 June 9 (Box 2, Image 563)
  - Bruce and O.D.S. in back yard, 1920 June 9 (Box 2, Image 564)
  - O.D.S. in back yard, 1920 June 9 (Box 2, Image 565)
  - R.O.S. and B.D.S., double exposure, 1920 June 9 (Box 2, Image 566)
  - Rose bush in back yard, 1920 June 9 (Box 2, Image 567)
  - O.D.S., B.D.S and R.O.S. in back yard, 1920 June 9 (Box 2, Image 568)
  - [Untitled] 1920 June 12 (Box 2, Image 569)
  - Bruce on chamber, 1920 June 12 (Box 2, Image 570)
  - Bruce and Thelma, front steps, 1920 June 22 (Box 2, Image 571)
  - Group on front steps, 1920 June 22 (Box 2, Image 572)
  - Bruce of chamber, 1920 June 24 (Box 2, Image 573)
  - [Untitled] 1920 June 24 (Box 2, Image 574)
  - [Untitled] 1920 June 24 (Box 2, Image 575)
  - [Untitled] 1920 June 24 (Box 2, Image 576)
  - Bruce on front porch, 1920 June 26 (Box 2, Image 577)
  - Bruce on front porch, 1920 June 26 (Box 2, Image 578)
  - Bruce on back porch, 1920 June 26 (Box 2, Image 579)
  - Bruce on back porch, 1920 June (Box 2, Image 580)
  - Bruce, Thelma, and Lois in back yard, 1920 June (Box 2, Image 581)
  - Bruce in back yard, 1920 June (Box 2, Image 582)
  - Bruce and O.D.S. in back yard, 1920 June (Box 2, Image 583)
  - Bruce in back yard, 1920 June (Box 2, Image 584)
  - O.D.S., B.D.S, Thelma, and Lois in back yard, 1920 June (Box 2, Image 585)
  - O.D.S., B.D.S. and R.O.S. in back yard, 1920 June (Box 2, Image 586)
  - Bruce, Thelma, and Lois in back yard, 1920 June (Box 2, Image 587)
  - July 4th decorations on house, 1920 July 5 (Box 2, Image 588)
  - Bruce with sparkler on front [porch], 1920 July 5 (Box 2, Image 589)
  - Bruce and O.D.S. with sparklers, 1920 July 5 (Box 2, Image 590)
  - Orphans from church, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Sept. 26 (Box 2, Image 591)
  - Orphans from church, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Sept. 26 (Box 2, Image 592)
  - Orphans from church, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Sept. 26 (Box 2, Image 593)
  - Bruce and Maud, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Sept. (Box 2, Image 594)
  - Bruce, Maud, and cats, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Sept. (Box 2, Image 595)
  - Bruce and cats, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Sept. (Box 2, Image 596)
  - Bruce, Maud, and cats, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Sept. (Box 2, Image 597)
  - Bruce and Cox in Buggy, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Sept. (Box 2, Image 598)
  - East from cousin Albert's house, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Sept. (Box 2, Image 599)
  - East from cousin Albert's house, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Sept. (Box 2, Image 600)
  - Bruce on porch, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Sept. (Box 2, Image 601)
  - B.D.S., O.D.S., and R.O.S., Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Sept. (Box 2, Image 602)
  - B.D.S. and R.O.S., Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Sept. (Box 2, Image 603)
  - B.D.S. and O.D.S., Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Sept. (Box 2, Image 604)
  - Bruce and cousin Daisy, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Sept. (Box 2, Image 605)
  - Aunt [Bob] on porch, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Sept. (Box 2, Image 606)
  - Bruce on porch, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Sept. 28 (Box 2, Image 607)
  - Bruce pushing toys on porch, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Sept. 28 (Box 2, Image 608)
  - Bruce on bicycle, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Sept. 29 (Box 2, Image 609)
  - Front lawn, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Sept. 30 (Box 2, Image 610)
  - East lawn, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Sept. 30 (Box 2, Image 611)
  - Administration building, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Oct. 1 (Box 2, Image 612)
  - Orphans going to church, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Oct. 3 (Box 2, Image 613)
  - Woods behind farm, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Oct. 3 (Box 2, Image 614)
  - In woods behind [farm], Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Oct. 3 (Box 2, Image 615)
  - Road in woods, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Oct. 3 (Box 2, Image 616)
  - Glenwood and [blank space], Raleigh, N.C., 1920 Oct. 3 (Box 2, Image 617)
  - Orphans coming from church, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Oct. 3 (Box 2, Image 618)
  - Old Buck, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Oct. 4 (Box 2, Image 619)
  - Bruce on Old Buck, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Oct. 4 (Box 2, Image 620)
  - Bruce on tennis court, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Oct. (Box 2, Image 621)
  - Bruce on tennis court, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Oct. (Box 2, Image 622)
  - Bruce on tennis court, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Oct. (Box 2, Image 623)
  - Ready to leave, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Oct. 8 (Box 2, Image 624)
  - Ready to leave, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Oct. 8 (Box 2, Image 625)
  - Ready to leave, B.D.S., Cousin Alma's, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Oct. 8 (Box 2, Image 626)
  - Bedie [Obediende?] and Maud, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Oct. 8 (Box 2, Image 627)
  - Cousin Alma's house, Raleigh, N.C., 1920 Oct. 9 (Box 2, Image 628)
  - Cousin Albert and Bruce, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Oct. 10 (Box 2, Image 629)
  - O.D.S., B.D.S, and R.O.S., Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Oct. 10 (Box 2, Image 630)
  - Cousin Alma and Bruce, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Oct. 10 (Box 2, Image 631)
  - Group, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Oct. 10 (Box 2, Image 632)
  - Maud and Bruce, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Oct. 10 (Box 2, Image 633)
  - Bruce on porch, Meth. Orph. Raleigh, 1920 Oct. 10 (Box 2, Image 634)
  - Bruce in yard, Raleigh, N.C., 1920 Oct. 12 (Box 2, Image 635)
  - Bruce in yard, Raleigh, N.C., 1920 Oct. 12 (Box 2, Image 636)
  - Bruce and Bedie, Raleigh, N.C., 1920 Oct. 14 (Box 2, Image 637)
  - Bruce and R.C.S., Raleigh, N.C., 1920 Oct. 14 (Box 2, Image 638)
  - Bruce and Zylphia, Raleigh, N.C., 1920 Oct. 14 (Box 2, Image 639)
  - Bruce and Zylphia, Raleigh, N.C., 1920 Oct. 14 (Box 2, Image 640)
  - William, Miss Calvart, Cousin Alma, and Bruce, R.R. station, Raleigh, 1920 Oct. 18 (Box 2, Image 641)
  - O.D.S., B.D.S., and R.O.S. at R.R. station, Raleigh, 1920 Oct. 18 (Box 2, Image 642)
  - Bruce in cotton patch near Goldsboro, N.C., 1920 Oct. 20 (Box 2, Image 643)
  - Bruce in cotton patch near Goldsboro, N.C., 1920 Oct. 20 (Box 2, Image 644)
  - Street in Wilson, N.C., 1920 Oct. 20 (Box 2, Image 645)
  - House in Wilson, N.C., 1920 Oct. 20 (Box 2, Image 646)
  - Grove in La Grange, N.C., 1920 Oct. 22 (Box 2, Image 647)
  - Grove in La Grange, N.C., 1920 Oct. 22 (Box 2, Image 648)
  - La Grange, N.C., 1920 Oct. 22 (Box 2, Image 649)
  - Aunt Kate [Issler?]'s house, La Grange, N.C., 1920 Oct. 22 (Box 2, Image 650)
  - Cousin Kate, Cousin Laurie, and Daisy Smith, La Grange, N.C., 1920 Oct. 22 (Box 2, Image 651)
  - Group, La Grange, N.C., 1920 Oct. 22 (Box 2, Image 652)
  - La Grange, N.C., 1920 Oct. 22 (Box 2, Image 653)
  - La Grange (blank), 1920 Oct. 22 (Box 2, Image 654)
  - Bedie and Daisy Smith, La Grange, N.C., 1920 Oct. 22 (Box 2, Image 655)
  - La Grange, N.C., 1920 Oct. 22 (Box 2, Image 656)
  - Freight station, La Grange, N.C., 1920 Oct. 22 (Box 2, Image 657)
  - La Grange, N.C., 1920 Oct. 22 (Box 2, Image 658)
  - Freight station, Fremont, N.C., 1920 Oct. 24 (Box 2, Image 659)
  - Fremont Academy, 1920 Oct. 24 (Box 2, Image 660)
  - Fremont Academy, 1920 Oct. 24 (Box 2, Image 661)
  - Bruce at Edmunson's Spring, Fremont, 1920 Oct. 24 (Box 2, Image 662)
  - Bruce at Edmunson's Spring, Fremont, 1920 Oct. 24 (Box 2, Image 663)
  - J.B. Hooks home place, Fremont, 1920 Oct. 24 (Box 2, Image 664)
  - Group at Edmunson's Spring, Fremont, 1920 Oct. 24 (Box 2, Image 665)
  - Bruce near Edmunson's Spring, Fremont, 1920 Oct. 24 (Box 2, Image 666)
  - Bruce in pine tree, Edmunson's Spring, Fremont, 1920 Oct. 24 (Box 2, Image 667)
  - Bruce in sand, Edmunson's Spring, Fremont, 1920 Oct. 24 (Box 2, Image 668)
  - Bruce and John, Edmunson's Spring, Fremont, 1920 Oct. 24 (Box 2, Image 669)
  - J.B. Hooks home place, Fremont, 1920 Oct. 24 (Box 2, Image 670)
  - Cousin Laurie's Home, Goldsboro, 1920 Oct. 26 (Box 2, Image 671)
  - Mulberry Street, Goldsboro, 1920 Oct. 26 (Box 2, Image 672)
  - Filling station, Goldsboro, 1920 Oct. 26 (Box 2, Image 673)
  - Street, Goldsboro, N.C., 1920 Oct. 29 (Box 2, Image 674)
  - Street, Goldsboro, N.C., 1920 Oct. 29 (Box 2, Image 675)
  - Street, Goldsboro, N.C., 1920 Oct. 29 (Box 2, Image 676)
  - Union Station, Goldsboro, N.C., 1920 Oct. 29 (Box 2, Image 677)
  - Southern train, Goldsboro, N.C., 1920 Oct. 29 (Box 2, Image 678)
  - Tobacco warehouse, Goldsboro, N.C., 1920 Oct. 30 (Box 2, Image 679)
  - Load of cotton, Goldsboro, N.C., 1920 Oct. 30 (Box 2, Image 680)
  - Border hooks, Goldsboro, N.C., 1920 Oct. 30 (Box 2, Image 681)
  - Union Station, Goldsboro, N.C., 1920 Oct. 30 (Box 2, Image 682)
  - La Grange, N.C. (from train), 1920 Oct. 30 (Box 2, Image 683)
  - La Grange, N.C. (from train), 1920 Oct. 30 (Box 2, Image 684)
  - Kinston, N.C (from train), 1920 Oct. 30 (Box 2, Image 685)
  - Kinston, N.C (from train), 1920 Oct. 30 (Box 2, Image 686)
  - Neuse River below Kinston (from train), 1920 Oct. 30 (Box 2, Image 687)
  - Bruce on sand, Beaufort, N.C., 1920 Nov. 1 (Box 2, Image 688)
  - Bruce on sand, Beaufort, N.C., 1920 Nov. 1 (Box 2, Image 689)
  - Bruce and R.O.S. on breakwater, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 1 (Box 2, Image 690)
  - Fish nets, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 2 (Box 2, Image 691)
  - Main Street, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 2 (Box 2, Image 692)
  - Children on breakwater, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 2 (Box 2, Image 693)
  - Water front, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 4 (Box 2, Image 694)
  - Biological laboratory, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 4 (Box 2, Image 695)
  - Beaufort from sound, 1920 Nov. 4 (Box 2, Image 696)
  - Beaufort and laboratory from sound, 1920 Nov. 4 (Box 2, Image 697)
  - Life guard station 191, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 4 (Box 2, Image 698)
  - Beafort from Fort Beach, 1920 Nov. 4 (Box 2, Image 699)
  - Life guanrd station, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 4 (Box 2, Image 700)
  - Beaufort from sound, 1920 Nov. 6 (Box 2, Image 701)
  - Bruce and Bedie on Fort Beach, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 6 (Box 2, Image 702)
  - Bruce and Bedie on Fort Beach, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 6 (Box 2, Image 703)
  - Bruce and R.O.S. on Fort Beach, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 6 (Box 2, Image 704)
  - Bruce on Fort Beach, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 6 (Box 2, Image 705)
  - Bruce and R.O.S. on Fort Beach, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 6 (Box 2, Image 706)
  - Bruce and R.O.S. on Fort Beach, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 6 (Box 2, Image 707)
  - Bruce and Bedie on Fort Beach, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 6 (Box 2, Image 708)
  - Bruce on Fort Beach, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 6 (Box 2, Image 709)
  - Bruce on Fort Beach, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 6 (Box 2, Image 710)
  - Bruce on Fort Beach, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 6 (Box 2, Image 711)
  - Clam beds, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 8 (Box 2, Image 712)
  - Clam beds and sail boad, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 8 (Box 2, Image 713)
  - Bruce and Bedie in boat, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 8 (Box 2, Image 714)
  - Bruce and R.O.S. in boat, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 8 (Box 2, Image 715)
  - Clam beds, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 8 (Box 2, Image 716)
  - Barrel factory, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 8 (Box 2, Image 717)
  - Shelton's house, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 8 (Box 2, Image 718)
  - Near Shelton's house, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 8 (Box 2, Image 719)
  - Brother Will's factory, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 8 (Box 2, Image 720)
  - Yacht anchored off Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 9 (Box 2, Image 721)
  - Draw bridge, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 9 (Box 2, Image 722)
  - Beaufort from sound, 1920 Nov. 9 (Box 2, Image 723)
  - Train on bridge, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 9 (Box 2, Image 724)
  - Train on Bridge, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 9 (Box 2, Image 725)
  - Bruce in swing, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 10 (Box 2, Image 726)
  - Bruce in side yard, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 10 (Box 2, Image 727)
  - Lunch at Fort, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 10 (Box 2, Image 728)
  - Lunch at Fort, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 10 (Box 2, Image 729)
  - Bruce and R.O.S., Fort Beach, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 10 (Box 2, Image 730)
  - Near Fort Macon, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 10 (Box 2, Image 731)
  - Fort Macon, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 10 (Box 2, Image 732)
  - Fort Macon, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 10 (Box 2, Image 733)
  - Fort Macon, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 10 (Box 2, Image 734)
  - Fort Macon, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 10 (Box 2, Image 735)
  - Life guard station 191, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 10 (Box 2, Image 736)
  - Life guard station 191, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 10 (Box 2, Image 737)
  - Bruce and Bedie on Fort Beach, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 10 (Box 2, Image 738)
  - Bruce and R.O.S. in boat on Fort Beach, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 10 (Box 2, Image 739)
  - Bruce and Bedie in boat in on Fort Beach, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 10 (Box 2, Image 740)
  - Beaufort from Fort Beach, 1920 Nov. 10 (Box 2, Image 741)
  - Zylphia's house, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 14 (Box 2, Image 742)
  - Street near Zylphia's house, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 14 (Box 2, Image 743)
  - R.R. station, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 14 (Box 2, Image 744)
  - Court house, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 14 (Box 2, Image 745)
  - R.R. station, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 14 (Box 2, Image 746)
  - R.R. station, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 14 (Box 2, Image 747)
  - Sound from R.R. station, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 14 (Box 2, Image 748)
  - Marsh Street, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 749)
  - Fish nets, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 750)
  - Water front, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 751)
  - Main Street, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 752)
  - Street, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 753)
  - Street, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 754)
  - Machine shops, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 755)
  - Street, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 756)
  - M. E. Church, Anne St., Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 757)
  - Street, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 758)
  - Zylphia's sitting room, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 759)
  - Bruce and William, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 760)
  - Alice Darden, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 761)
  - Bruce and William, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 762)
  - Alice and Bruce, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 763)
  - Zylphia, Alice, William, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 764)
  - Zylphia, Alice, William, and Bruce, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 765)
  - Bruce and Bedie, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 766)
  - Bruce and Aunt Milly, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 767)
  - Bruce on train, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 768)
  - Group at station, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 769)
  - Biological laboratory, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 770)
  - Bridge from train, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 771)
  - Bridge from train, Beaufort, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 772)
  - Bridge from train, Morehead City, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 773)
  - Bridge from train, Morehead City, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 774)
  - Morehead City, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 775)
  - Morehead City, station, 1920 Nov. 17 (Box 2, Image 776)
  - Christmas toys, Ruxton Avenue, 1920 Dec. 25 (Box 2, Image 777)
  - Christmas toys, Ruxton Avenue, 1920 Dec. 25 (Box 2, Image 778)
  - Christmas toys, Ruxton Avenue, 1920 Dec. 25 (Box 2, Image 779)
  - Polly and Bruce, 1920 Dec. 25 (Box 2, Image 780)
  - Bruce and Emyline, Loch Ruren, 1920 June (Box 2, Image 781)
  - Bruce and Emyline, Loch Ruren, 1920 June (Box 2, Image 782)
  - Bruce and Emyline in Ford sedan, Loch Ruren, 1920 June (Box 2, Image 783)
  - Bruce and Emyline near stream, Loch Ruren, 1920 June (Box 2, Image 784)
  - Bruce and Emyline in yard, Ruxton Avenue, 1920 June (Box 2, Image 785)
  - Bruce and Emyline in yard, Ruxton Avenue, 1920 June (Box 2, Image 786)
  - Bruce in auto, Ruxton Avenue, 1921 (Box 2, Image 787)
  - Bruce on porch, Ruxton Avenue, 1921 (Box 2, Image 788)
  - Bruce on porch, Ruxton Avenue, 1921 (Box 2, Image 789)
  - Bruce on porch, Ruxton Avenue, 1921 (Box 2, Image 790)
  - Bruce and R.O.S., Ruxton Avenue,Winter 1921 (Box 2, Image 791)
  - Bruce on Ford sedan, Ruxton Avenue,Winter 1921 (Box 2, Image 792)
  - Bruce and Polly, Ruxton Avenue,Winter 1921 (Box 2, Image 793)
  - Bedie and Polly, Ruxton Avenue, Winter 1921 (Box 2, Image 794)
  - Bruce, Ruxton Avenue,Winter 1921 (Box 2, Image 795)
  - Mr. Gross, Ruxton Avenue,Winter 1921 (Box 2, Image 796)
  - Bruce, Ruxton Avenue,Winter 1921 (Box 2, Image 797)
  - Bruce, Ruxton Avenue, 1922 (Box 2, Image 798)
  - Bruce, Ruxton Avenue, 1922 (Box 2, Image 799)
  - Bruce and Bedie, Ruxton Avenue, 1922 (Box 2, Image 800)
  - Index cards, 801-911 (Box 2)
  - Bruce and Bedie, Ruxton Avenue, 1922 (Box 2, Image 801)
  - Bruce and R.O.S., Ruxton Avenue, 1922 (Box 2, Image 802)
  - Bruce and R.O.S., Ruxton Avenue, 1922 (Box 2, Image 803)
  - Bruce in yard, Ruxton Avenue, 1922 (Box 2, Image 804)
  - Bruce, Ruxton Avenue, 1922 (Box 2, Image 805)
  - Bruce, Ruxton Avenue, 1922 (Box 2, Image 806)
  - Bedie, Ruxton Avenue, 1922 (Box 2, Image 807)
  - Bedie and Bruce, Ruxton Avenue, 1922 (Box 2, Image 808)
  - Bruce and Dorothy, Ruxton Avenue, 1922 (Box 2, Image 809)
  - Bedie, Ruxton Avenue, 1922 (Box 2, Image 810)
  - Shady Side, 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 811)
  - Shady Side, 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 812)
  - Bruce and R.O.S., Shady Side, 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 813)
  - Shady Side, 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 814)
  - Shady Side, 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 815)
  - Shady Side, 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 816)
  - Shady Side, 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 817)
  - Road, Shady Side, 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 818)
  - River, Shady Side, 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 819)
  - [Untitled] 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 820)
  - Bedie and Bruce, Shady Side, 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 821)
  - Bedie and Bruce, Shady Side, 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 822)
  - R.O.S. and Bruce, Shady Side, 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 823)
  - [Steamer?] Emma Giles, Shady Side, 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 824)
  - [Steamer?] Emma Giles, Shady Side, 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 825)
    The passenger steamer Emma Giles was a popular sight-seeing ship that served Baltimore and points east along the West River, Tolchester Beach, and other points.
  - Bedie and Bruce, Shady Side, 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 826)
  - Bedie and Bruce, Shady Side, 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 827)
  - R.O.S. and Bruce, Shady Side, 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 828)
  - R.O.S., Bedie, and Bruce, Shady Side, 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 829)
  - St. Polly, Shady Side, 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 830)
  - Bedie, R.O.S., Bruce, Shady Side, 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 831)
  - [Untitled] 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 832)
  - [Untitled] 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 833)
  - [Untitled] 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 834)
  - [Untitled] 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 835)
  - Gettysburg, 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 836)
  - Gettysburg, 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 837)
  - Lee Monument, Gettysburg, 1922 Aug. (Box 2, Image 838)
  - Towson House, 1923 June (Box 2, Image 839)
  - Towson House, north side, 1923 June (Box 2, Image 840)
  - Towson House, back, 1923 June (Box 2, Image 841)
  - Towson House, west angle, 1923 June (Box 2, Image 842)
  - Towson House, Bruce by office, 1923 June (Box 3, Image 843)
  - Towson House, R.O.S. by office, 1923 June (Box 3, Image 844)
  - Towson House, front, 1923 June (Box 3, Image 845)
  - Church and Rev. Lee's house, Towson, 1923 winter (Box 3, Image 846)
  - Garage, Towson, 1923 winter (Box 3, Image 847)
  - Front of house, Towson, 1923 winter (Box 3, Image 848)
  - Front of house, Towson, 1923 winter (Box 3, Image 849)
  - Bruce, Towson, 1923 winter (Box 3, Image 850)
  - Bruce, Towson, 1923 winter (Box 3, Image 851)
  - Bedie and Bruce, Towson, 1924 summer (Box 3, Image 852)
  - Bedie and Bruce, Towson, 1924 summer (Box 3, Image 853)
  - Bruce in auto and apple tree, 1924 summer (Box 3, Image 854)
  - Bruce in back yard, 1924 summer (Box 3, Image 855)
  - Bruce up tree, 1924 summer (Box 3, Image 856)
  - Bruce up tree, 1924 summer (Box 3, Image 857)
  - [Untitled; faded image of individual, probably Bruce Darden], 1924 (Box 3, Image 858)
  - [Untitled; faded image of individual, female?], [1924?] (Box 3, Image 859)
  - Bruce in kiddie car, [1924] (Box 3, Image 860)
  - Bruce in kiddie car, [1924] (Box 3, Image 861)
  - Kindergarten auto, 1924 (Box 3, Image 862)
  - R.O.S. and Bedie, [1924] (Box 3, Image 863)
  - Bedie, [1924] (Box 3, Image 864)
  - Bruce and Jackie Croghan, [1924] (Box 3, Image 865)
  - Bruce and Jackie Croghan, [1924] (Box 3, Image 866)
  - Bruce and Jackie Croghan, [1924] (Box 3, Image 867)
  - Bruce and Jackie Croghan, [1924] (Box 3, Image 868)
  - Bruce and Rudolph in kitchen, 1930 (Box 3, Image 869)
  - Bruce and Rudolph by office, 1930 (Box 3, Image 870)
  - R.O.S. and Rudolph by office, 1930 (Box 3, Image 871)
  - Bedie and Rudolph by office, 1930 (Box 3, Image 872)
  - Bruce and Rudolph by office, 1930 (Box 3, Image 873)
  - R.O.S. by Bunham Spring, 1932 Aug. 14 (Box 3, Image 874)
  - Bedie by Bunham Spring, 1932 Aug. 14 (Box 3, Image 875)
  - Bedie by Bunham Spring, 1932 Aug. 14 (Box 3, Image 876)
  - Bedie, Helen, Joe Frazer, Bruce, Shelman Jecks, 1932 Aug. 14 (Box 3, Image 877)
  - Bruce washing in Elk River, 1932 Aug. 15 (Box 3, Image 878)